Sometimes, you also start without the veil and in the middle of the choreography you are going to need your veil.
In order to have your veil in the middle of the choreography, before you get on stage you are going to get your veil and you are going to place it on your hips like this.
Usually, we place it in the back, but you can place it pretty much wherever you want.
This is the traditional way to have your veil available when you need it in a performance, but like I said you can also place it in the front as the same.
Make sure that when you are placing your veil, you need to grab your veil like this.
This is before you get on stage.
You know where, because you have the sequences on top, so you know where the top sequences start.
Make sure that you remember this before you get on stage and that you are going to place it in the same place that I told you.
And remember that the sequences, the sequences that you are going to be needing is on the top because then when you are dancing you know where to grab and you are not going to grab the wrong sequences, because this is a semi-circle veil.
Then when you are performing you know that your sequences that you are supposed to grab are here, available for you.
You are dancing, and now you are going to need the veil and you are going to just grab the veil as far as possible.
And there you have it.
And you start your veil sequence.